[Music] I've been
running this shop for 10 years, and the
income is decent for a small town.
[Music]
Right now, my son is only 4 years old. As he grows
older, many
other expenses will increase, such as a
computer for his studies and a bicycle for going to school.
[Music]
A reliable company, ICICI Prudential
Life, will support you in meeting these needs. We bring to you a new-age
plan, ICICI Prudential Life, which will
provide you with a regular guaranteed income so that you can
fulfil all your dreams, big and small. If
you, like Pawan Kumar, want
a guaranteed income for your children on a lump sum amount on the policy maturity, then the
ICICI Prudential Life Prosperity Income option
offers you many benefits. If you
pay a premium of ₹75,000 every year for 10 years, then
after the premium payment term ends,
you will receive a
guaranteed income of ₹78,750 every year for the next 8 years.
In addition,
you will receive a lump sum amount on the policy maturity.  You will also be given a
gift for your children on their birthdays. If you want to gift them,
you can use the date feature. This
feature gives you the option that if you do
not need income in a particular year, you
can deposit that income in your savings wallet.
This deposited amount will keep growing
and you can withdraw it anytime. You can
use the feature whenever you want during the policy term
and you are
also protected with life cover for the entire policy term. So now,
like Pawan Kumar, you can fulfill
every need of your child with ICICI Prudential Samriddhi.
Choose ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance. Your trusted life insurance to fulfill every dream of you and your loved ones.
[Music]